Nothing starts until you take action.
If you have time to worry, then run!
Do I need a reason to want to help out a friend?
I'm Sonic, Sonic the Hedgehog.
I have no master, except the wind that blows free.
Merlina, every world has its end.
I know that's kind of sad, but...
That's why we gotta live life to the fullest in the time we have.
At least, that's what I figure.
I am...
The Creator!
The stories of this world are...
Mine!
If this is your world, then it's a world that I don't want any part of!
That's why I must do what I must do.
I am finished with you.
What is a world that goes on forever?
That sounds pretty smart.
That adventure's no fun if it's too easy.
You fool!
This no longer has anything to do with chivalry!
Get out of there!
Run!
It was never about chivalry for me.
I just gotta do what I've gotta do!
That's all!
Are you ready?
Ready for what?
If you remove that sword and defeat King Arthur with it,
you shall forever be the worst of knights, slayer of kings.
Guess I can't be the hero every time.
It's no use.
But why can't I defuse you?
Huh.
Because...
We're Sonic Heroes!
This is my power.
And I'm not using it to run away anymore.
I'm using it to protect...
my...
friends.
We're Sonic Heroes!
It's a troll-
This is my power.
And I'm not using it to run away anymore.
I'm using it to protect...
my...
friends.